Erhan Yaylali

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

+45 50 23 19 14

in linkedin.com/in/erhanyaylali

www.yaylali.net

erhanyaylali9@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a software developer with more than three and half years' experience in the field. As a person, I am great at collaborating, working as a team player and a very open-minded person. Besides developing websites, I have experience on working with UI/UX teams for design, handling SEO optimizations and communicating with customers. I am currently residing in Odense, Denmark.

SKILLS

JavaScript, jQuery . CSS and SASS

Detail Oriented

Problem solving (engineering)

React, Redux

Google Console and AWS
Good communication

Attention to detail

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering

Istanbul Technical University • 2016 – 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Hesehus A/S, Odense, Denmark

Frontend Developer • July 2022 - Present

- I am helping our customers to get better SEO results, have to them user friendly and accessible pages, high quality and sustainable software in technical development.
- By considering the budget and scope of project, I am helping customer to **determine roadmap** for upcoming times, to analyze the current problems, to find good solutions for requirements for needs.

Orion Innovation, Istanbul, Turkey

Full stack Developer • December 2021 - July 2022

- I implemented React Query system that improved the performance +30% than Redux system that was built.
- I integrated Google Cloud services for both frontend (React) and backend (Node JS) projects. I also implemented ORM for database in one of the layers, and Firebase DB for another.
- I integrated bidirectional communication between multiple layers by using Websocket.

Yapı Kredi Technology, İstanbul, Türkey

Full stack Developer • July 2021 - December 2021

- I was building intra webpages by using React, Java, MySQL technologies for the lawyers. I was also focusing on user experience and accessibility of the the page.
- By implementing unit tests, I helped the project got 90% coverage.

Ibtech, Gebze, Turkey

Jr Fullstack Developer • February 2021 - July.2021

• I created a new Micro react Project for a new requested feature. I also implemented Redux state system and Swagger to the project.